

JORGE SARRICOLEA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Email LinkedInd Mérida, Yucatán +52 938 109 5593

ABOUT ME	
----------	--

I am a Web Developer specialized in UI/UX Design, over 2 years of experience working on different projects. I am a Personal Finance and Technology enthusiast, always keeping up with the latest trends, and have the ability to learn anything I set my mind to.

Check my own page: jorgesarricolea.com

WORK EXPERIENCE ______

Photolens | September 2023 - October 2023

Link: Photolens

Photolens is project that allows the user to upload photos and display these photos as a digital photo album. I have used React to create visual components, as well as Bootstrap to make the design more appealing. On the Backend, I have set up a local server using Express and Node.js. Since it is a small application, I have decided to use MySQL as my database

The Movies APP | June 2023 - July 2023

Link: Movies-App

Developed with NextJS, TypeScript, and TailwindCSS. I used TheMovieDB API to fetch all the data displayed on the frontend of this project. This project was deployed with Vercel.

Web Developer | Datamatic Software | June 2022 - July 2022

LinkedIn: Datamatic Software

I worked on different projects, designing the user interface from scratch, adding new features, and utilizing backend workflows and reusable components for various projects.

Fullstack Developer | Jumwork | January 2018 - January 2022

Link: jumwork.com

I designed the whole brand, user experience and user interface from scratch on Bubble. Integration with Stripe API and others in backend process. Worked with different plugins, like Sendgrid and upgraded old pages to the new responsive engine.

EDUCATION ______

Computer System Engineering | August 2020 – Present

Instituto Tecnológico de Mérida

Platzi Certificates

Frontend Developer Course | 2022 HTML and CSS Practical Course | 2021 Software Engineering Fundamentals | 2021 Interface Design Course | 2020

SKILLS ______

Programming, frameworks and cloud

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, React, Boostrap, TailwindCSS, Jest, NodeJS, NextJS, Express, MySQL, PHP

Tools and design enverioment

Git Version Control, VSCode, Trello, Notion, Miro, Figma, Abobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop

Others

Conversational English, quick and continuous learning, adaptability, problem solving capacity, teamwork, leadership, communicative, creative, responsible, honest